module.exports = {
	config: {
		name: "Ø§Ø¹Ù„Ø§Ù…", // Name of command, it must be unique to identify with other commands
		version: "1.0", // Version of command
		author: "Eslam", // Author of command
		countDown: 5, // Time to wait before executing command again (seconds)
		role: 0, // Role of user to use this command (0: normal user, 1: admin box chat, 2: owner bot)
		shortDescription: {
			vi: "Ä‘Ã¢y lÃ  mÃ´ táº£ ngáº¯n cá»§a lá»‡nh",
			en: "Ù„Ø¹Ø¨Ø©"
		}, // Short description of command
		longDescription: {
			vi: "Ä‘Ã¢y lÃ  mÃ´ táº£ dÃ i cá»§a lá»‡nh",
			en: "this is long description of command"
		}, // Long description of command
		category: "categoryName", // Category of command
		guide: {
			vi: "Ä‘Ã¢y lÃ  hÆ°á»›ng dáº«n sá»­ dá»¥ng cá»§a lá»‡nh",
			en: "this is guide of command"
		} // Guide of command
	},

	langs: {
		vi: {
			hello: "xin chÃ o",
			helloWithName: "xin chÃ o, id facebook cá»§a báº¡n lÃ  %1"
		}, // Vietnamese language
		en: {
			hello: "hello world",
			helloWithName: "hello, your facebook id is %1"
		} // English language
	},

	// onStart is a function that will be executed when the command is executed
	onStart: async function ({ api, args, message, event, threadsData, usersData, dashBoardData, globalData, threadModel, userModel, dashBoardModel, globalModel, role, commandName, getLang }) {
		// YOUR CODE HERE
    
              let questions = [
            {
                  question: "  Ø§Ù„ÙˆÙ„Ø§ÙŠØ§Øª Ø§Ù„Ù…ØªØ­Ø¯Ø© Ø§Ù„Ø£Ù…Ø±ÙŠÙƒÙŠØ© ",
                  answer: "ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸"
                }, {
                  question: " Ø§Ù„Ù…Ù…Ù„ÙƒØ© Ø§Ù„Ù…ØªØ­Ø¯Ø©",
                  answer: "ðŸ‡¬ðŸ‡§"
                },
                {
                  question: " ÙØ±Ù†Ø³Ø§ ",
                  answer: "ðŸ‡«ðŸ‡·"
                }, {
                  question: " Ø£Ù„Ù…Ø§Ù†ÙŠØ§",
                  answer: "ðŸ‡©ðŸ‡ª"
                }, {
                  question: " Ø¥ÙŠØ·Ø§Ù„ÙŠØ§",
                  answer: "ðŸ‡®ðŸ‡¹"
                }, {
                  question: " Ø§Ù„ÙŠØ§Ø¨Ø§Ù†",
                  answer: "ðŸ‡¯ðŸ‡µ"
                }, {
                  question: " ÙƒÙ†Ø¯Ø§",
                  answer: "ðŸ‡¨ðŸ‡¦"
                }, {
                  question: " Ø§Ù„ØµÙŠÙ†",
                  answer: "ðŸ‡¨ðŸ‡³"
                }, {
                  question: " Ø±ÙˆØ³ÙŠØ§",
                  answer: "ðŸ‡·ðŸ‡º"
                }, {
                  question: " Ø§Ù„Ù‡Ù†Ø¯",
                  answer: "ðŸ‡®ðŸ‡³"
                }, {
                  question: " Ø£Ø³ØªØ±Ø§Ù„ÙŠØ§",
                  answer: "ðŸ‡¦ðŸ‡º"
                }, {
                  question: " Ø§Ù„Ø¨Ø±Ø§Ø²ÙŠÙ„",
                  answer: "ðŸ‡§ðŸ‡·"
                }, {
                  question: " Ø¬Ù†ÙˆØ¨ Ø£ÙØ±ÙŠÙ‚ÙŠØ§",
                  answer: "ðŸ‡¿ðŸ‡¦"
                }, {
                  question: " Ø§Ù„Ù…ÙƒØ³ÙŠÙƒ",
                  answer: "ðŸ‡²ðŸ‡½"
                }, {
                  question: " Ø¥Ø³Ø¨Ø§Ù†ÙŠØ§",
                  answer: "ðŸ‡ªðŸ‡¸"
                }, {
                  question: " ÙƒÙˆØ±ÙŠØ§ Ø§Ù„Ø¬Ù†ÙˆØ¨ÙŠØ©",
                  answer: "ðŸ‡°ðŸ‡·"
                }, {
                  question: " Ù†ÙŠØ¬ÙŠØ±ÙŠØ§",
                  answer: "ðŸ‡³ðŸ‡¬"
                }, {
                  question: " Ø¥ÙŠØ±Ø§Ù†",
                  answer: "ðŸ‡®ðŸ‡·"
                }, {
                  question: " ØªØ±ÙƒÙŠØ§",
                  answer: "ðŸ‡¹ðŸ‡·"
                }, {
                  question: " Ø§Ù„Ø£Ø±Ø¬Ù†ØªÙŠÙ†",
                  answer: "ðŸ‡¦ðŸ‡·"
                }, {
                  question: " Ø¨Ø§ÙƒØ³ØªØ§Ù†",
                  answer: "ðŸ‡µðŸ‡°"
                }, {
                  question: " Ø§Ù„ÙÙ„Ø¨ÙŠÙ†",
                  answer: "ðŸ‡µðŸ‡­"
                }, {
                  question: " Ø¥Ù†Ø¯ÙˆÙ†ÙŠØ³ÙŠØ§",
                  answer: "ðŸ‡®ðŸ‡©"
                }, {
                  question: " Ù…ØµØ±",
                  answer: "ðŸ‡ªðŸ‡¬"
                }, {
                  question: " ÙƒÙˆÙ„ÙˆÙ…Ø¨ÙŠØ§",
                  answer: "ðŸ‡¨ðŸ‡´"
                },    
              ];
              let randomIndex = Math.floor(Math.random() * questions.length);
              let randomQuestion = questions[randomIndex].question;
              let answer = questions[randomIndex].answer;
              api.sendMessage(randomQuestion, event.threadID, (err, messageInfo)=>{
                let stopListening = api.listenMqtt((err, event) => {
                if (err) return console.error(err);

                switch (event.type) {
                  case "message":
                    if(event.threadID === messageInfo.threadID){
                      if (event.body === answer) {               api.sendMessage("Ø¬Ù…ÙŠÙ„ Ø§Ù†Øª Ø³Ø±ÙŠØ¹", event.threadID, event.messageID);
                      return stopListening();
                    } else if (event.body === 'Ø§Ø¹Ù„Ø§Ù…') {
                      return stopListening();
                    }
                    api.markAsRead(event.threadID, (err) => {
                      if (err) console.log(err);
                    });
                    }

                    break;
                }
              });
              });

	}
};